Thank you very much. When I noticed at all, Senora C. Senores, I wanted to
start with my language, Spanish.
I was born in Spain and grew up in Latin America. In any rate, good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
First of all, allow me to congratulate and thank the handsome family for their
awesome job that they perform every year,
keeping alive the leadership of promoting and celebrating the leadership in our
international communities.
Congratulations to all the individuals, wonderful leaders in this body,
wonderful friends.
Today, I have the great honor to induct Carolyn Balogh to the International
Hall of Fame.
Everyone in this audience, majority, knows Carolyn as a great leader, as a
great businesswoman,
CFO, HR director, and vice president of their own family business, Marva Ng.
Also, a great leader in the Hawaiian community.
Tonight, in my short and brief remarks, only two minutes ago now, only a few of
us, and I am one of the lucky ones,
knew Carolyn's philanthropic role, vision, and support to the Spanish community.
I surprised Abby when I told her the story and I presented her fantasy. I knew
that she would be a winner.
I had the pleasure to meet Carolyn more than 20 years ago. We need to recognize
time pass.
We were together serving at the El Barrio Board of Directors. We are one of the
most successful Hispanic agencies in East North America.
She was, during those days, the first chair of the Programs Committee, and
under her leadership, the job placement requests extended expectations.
She was able to develop a great partnership with company owners searching for
employees to fill their job openings.
She also created a passing program for employees with transportation needs.
Additionally, Carolyn lived a girl, an after-school program at the elementary
level, including mentoring and tutoring.
And all of this was done in the different locations of the school system.
Carolyn is well known for her professionalism, for her high emotional
intelligence, and for her sensitivity and empathy toward others.
Her early education and empowering employees were two of her most notorious
passions. Please welcome Carolyn Varo.
[BLANK_AUDIO]